<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SOD Killer</string>
    <string name="description"><![CDATA[
        App is designed to fixed the SOD (Sleep of Death) issue that has plagued the Nexus 4.
        This is an app for my own use, however it might be useful for other users who are Nexus 4
        owners or owners of other devices that has the sleep of death problem.
        <br /><br />
        To enable, just click &quot;Enable SOD&quot;. This will create a wake lock and will not allow
        your device to sleep, which hopefully mean you are less likely to get the SOD issue. I feel
        sometimes if the device falls into deep sleep that it cannot be woken up and causes the SOD
        issue. Because the app keeps your device awake you will notice that the app will consume
        more battery, which is a trade off for having your phone turn on.
        <br /><br />
        If you still experience problems you can keep SOD Killer running in the foreground.
        This will set a notification in your notification tray.
        <br /><br /><strong>Permission</strong><br />
        Run at startup - So if you restart the phone and you have allowed the app to keep the
        wakelock, the program will keep a wakelock.
        <br /><br />
        Prevent phone from sleeping - We are keeping a wakelock, so this is obvious....
        <br /><br /><strong>Donate</strong><br />
        If this app works for you and you want to donate some money to me please click the below
        PayPal link and give whatever you want. <br />Thanks!!!
        <br /><br />
        <a href="https://www.paypal.me/RichardTan/">https://www.paypal.me/RichardTan</a>
        <br /><br /><br /><strong>Website</strong><br />
        <a href="http://www.justexperiment.com">http://www.justexperiment.com</a>
        <br /><br /><strong>GitHub</strong><br />
        <a href="https://github.com/richardtan/SODKiller">https://github.com/richardtan/SODKiller</a>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="enable_sod">Enable SOD?</string>
    <string name="keep_foreground">Keep in the foreground?</string>
    <string name="notification_text">SOD Killer is running</string>
</resources>
